

Artur Pazyniuk

FRONTEND DEVELOPER, 7 YEARS

Contact Details

+373 (61) 014938 artur.pazyniuk.dev@gmail.com

Social Links

github linkedln telegram

Languages

English - Fluent Ukrainian - Native

Summary

A passionate frontend developer with **7+** years of experience in **React**, **Next.js** and **Typescript**. Committed to continuous learning and staying up-to-date with the latest technologies.

Languages: TypeScript, JavaScript.

Frameworks: React, Next.js, Vue, Redux, MobX, Zustand. **Testing**: Jest, React Testing Library, Cypress, Unit Testing.

Design System: Material UI, Chakra UI, AntDesign, Tailwind, Bootstrap.

Other: Webpack, Storybook, ReactQuery, i18n, WebSocket, Nx, REST Api, HTML&CSS, Git,

GraphQL, Docker, CI/CD, Scrum/Agile.

Employment History

Senior Frontend Developer

NDA

December 2022 - Present

Product description:

Al-Powered Innovation Solutions B2B startup from Silicon Valley. Designed to help business collecting data from various sources (PDF, PowerPoint, Web), processing this data and displaying it to the customer in a well-organized way.

My achievements:

- Built frontend application from scratch, following architectural patterns, ensuring great performance and scalability.
- Developed frontend anticipation mechanism that pre-loads content in advance, based on a user's behavioural patterns, reducing waiting from 1-2 minutes to 10-20 seconds.
- Covered frontend application with E2E tests and Sentry monitoring to ensure app's stability, eliminating the need to hire a QA.

Senior Frontend Developer

Alar Development

October 2020 - November 2022

Product description:

A collaboration platform startup designed for teams and organizations. It offers real-time messaging, file sharing, and integration with various third-party apps to streamline workflow and improve productivity.

My achievements:

- Decoupled frontend-backend monolyth in 2 weeks, when it was estimated for 3 month.
- Developed real-time update feature to show incoming messages without the need to refresh the page, using WebSocket.
- Introduced TypeScript to the frontend application, improving type safety and decreasing total monthly bugs quantity by 30%.

Middle Frontend Developer

OS system

July 2018 - October 2020

Projects description:

Various projects in different business domains, such as: Real Estate, EdTech, Social Media and Crypto, delivering scalable frontend solutions.

My achievements:

- Resolved over 50 critical production bugs, as a part of a "Fast Response Team".
- Communicated with product owners and project managers, developing features as per their requirements within estimated time frames.
- Developed and enhanced the frontend architecture and components of projects, focusing on both expanding existing features and introducing new ones.

Education

Bachelor's degree

Kyiv State University of Infrastructure and Technologies September 2015 - May 2019